Guide to the Willard Dickerman Straight papers, 1825-1925.
Straight, Willard Dickerman papers, 1825-1925.
- Visual Materials
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Escort 1908 (Box 62, Folder 39)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Landscapes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 39)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Village Scenes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 39)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Escort 1908 (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Rural Scenes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Transporation, Oxcarts 1908 (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Transportation, Horses 1908 (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Ships 1908 (Box 62, Folder 41)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Bamboo 1908 (Box 62, Folder 41)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 41)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Escort 1908 (Box 62, Folder 41)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Landscapes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 41)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Militia 1908 (Box 62, Folder 41)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 42)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Chinese Army, Calvary 1908 (Box 62, Folder 42)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Christian Graveyard 1908 (Box 62, Folder 42)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Escort 1908 (Box 62, Folder 42)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Gillis, J.V. 1908 (Box 62, Folder 42)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Landscapes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 42)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Transportation, Horsecarts 1908 (Box 62, Folder 42)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Transportation, Horses 1908 (Box 62, Folder 42)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Architecture, Exterior 1908 (Box 62, Folder 43)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 43)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Ceremonies 1908 (Box 62, Folder 44)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 44)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - City Scenes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 44)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - River Scenes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 44)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Rooftops 1908 (Box 62, Folder 44)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Transportation, Houseboats 1908 (Box 62, Folder 44)
  - Manuchurian Trip
    - Boats 1908 (Box 62, Folder 44)
  - Manchurian Trip, Scenes of Chinese Life
    - Vendors 1908 (Box 62, Folder 45)
  - Manchurian Trip, Scenes of Chinese Life (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 45)
  - Manchurian Trip, Scenes of Chinese Life (annotated)
    - Crime and Punishment 1908 (Box 62, Folder 45)
  - Manchurian Trip, Scenes of Chinese Life (annotated)
    - Occupations 1908 (Box 62, Folder 45)
  - Manchurian Trip, Scenes of Chinese Life (annotated)
    - Street Performers 1908 (Box 62, Folder 45)
  - Manchurian Trip, Scenes of Chinese Life (annotated)
    - Camel Caravans 1908 (Box 62, Folder 46)
  - Manchurian Trip, Scenes of Chinese Life (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 46)
  - Manchurian Trip, Scenes of Chinese Life (annotated)
    - Chinese Army 1908 (Box 62, Folder 46)
  - Manchurian Trip, Scenes of Chinese Life (annotated)
    - Street Scenes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 46)
  - Manchurian Trip, Scenes of Chinese Life (annotated)
    - Transportation, Camel Caravans 1908 (Box 62, Folder 46)
  - Manchurian Trip, Scenes of Chinese Life (annotated)
    - Vendors 1908 (Box 62, Folder 46)
  - Manchuria
    - Architecture, Exterior 1908 (Box 62, Folder 47)
  - Manchuria
    - Architecture, Interior 1908 (Box 62, Folder 47)
  - Manchuria
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 47)
  - Manchuria
    - Gates 1908 (Box 62, Folder 47)
  - Manchuria
    - Pagodas 1908 (Box 62, Folder 47)
  - Manuchuria
    - Bridges 1908 (Box 62, Folder 47)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - Palaces 1907 (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - Peiling Tomb, Mukden 1907 (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners 1907 (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1907 c. (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - Arnell, Charles J. 1907 c. (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - Marvin, George D. 1907c. (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - Sculpture 1907c. (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1907c. (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - Temple of Heaven, Mukden Palace 1907c. (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - Tombs 1907c. (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - U.S. Consulate, Mukden 1907c. (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Mukden (annotated, autographed)
    - China, Manchuria, Mukden 1907c. (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Macao
    - Church of St. John, Macao n.d. (Box 62, Folder 49)
  - Macao
    - Fishing Industry n.d. (Box 62, Folder 49)
  - Macao
    - Harbors n.d. (Box 62, Folder 49)
  - Macao
    - Macao n.d. (Box 62, Folder 49)
  - Macao
    - Occupations n.d. (Box 62, Folder 49)
  - Macao
    - Seascapes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 49)
  - Macao
    - Street Scenes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 49)
  - Macao
    - Transportation, Junks n.d. (Box 62, Folder 49)
  - Hankow and Hanyang
    - Street Scenes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 50)
  - Hankow and Hanyang
    - Transporation, Sailboats n.d. (Box 62, Folder 50)
  - Hankow and Hanyang
    - Yangtze River n.d. (Box 62, Folder 50)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - China, Hankow n.d. (Box 62, Folder 50)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - China, Hanyang n.d. (Box 62, Folder 50)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - City Scenes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 50)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - Docks n.d. (Box 62, Folder 50)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - River Scenes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 50)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Boats n.d. (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Bridges n.d. (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Chang Temple, Canton n.d. (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - China, Canton n.d. (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Docks n.d. (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Flower Pagoda, Canton n.d. (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Pagodas n.d. (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Ports n.d. (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Seascapes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Street Scenes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Temple of Five-Hundred Genjii, Canton n.d. (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Temples n.d. (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Transportation, Junks n.d. (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Transportation, Steamships n.d. (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Hankow and Hanyang (annotated)
    - Teahouses n.d. (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Hankow and Hanyang (annotated)
    - Transporation, Sailboats n.d. (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Hankow and Hanyang (annotated)
    - Yangtze River n.d. (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - Canals n.d. (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - China, Hankow n.d. (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - China, Hanyang n.d. (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - China, Wuhu n.d. (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - City Scenes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - Docks n.d. (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - Han River n.d. (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - Lumber n.d. (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - Pagodas n.d. (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - Porcelain Trade n.d. (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - River Scenes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Hankow and Hanyang(annotated)
    - Rooftops n.d. (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Boats n.d. (Box 62, Folder 53)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - China, Canton n.d. (Box 62, Folder 53)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Docks n.d. (Box 62, Folder 53)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - Pearl River n.d. (Box 62, Folder 53)
  - Canton (annotated)
    - River Scenes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 53)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - Peiling Tomb, Mukden 1907 (Box 62, Folder 54)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Groups 1907 (Box 62, Folder 54)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1907 c. (Box 62, Folder 54)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - Government Officials 1907c. (Box 62, Folder 54)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - Sculpture 1907c. (Box 62, Folder 54)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - Temple of Heaven, Mukden Palace 1907c. (Box 62, Folder 54)
  - Mukden (annotated, autographed)
    - China, Manchuria, Mukden 1907c. (Box 62, Folder 54)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - China, Changchow n.d. (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - China, Chiu-Chiang n.d. (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - China, Nanking n.d. (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - China, Shanghai n.d. (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - China, Soochow n.d. (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - Lake Hangchow n.d. (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - Landscapes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - Pagodas n.d. (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Chinese n.d. (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - River Scenes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - Street Scenes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - Transporation, Sailboats n.d. (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - Yangtze River n.d. (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - China, Chiu-Chiang n.d. (Box 62, Folder 56)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - China, Shanghai n.d. (Box 62, Folder 56)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - Lung-Hua Pagoda n.d. (Box 62, Folder 56)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - Orphan Island n.d. (Box 62, Folder 56)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - Pagodas n.d. (Box 62, Folder 56)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - River Scenes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 56)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - Topography n.d. (Box 62, Folder 56)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - Transportation, Junks n.d. (Box 62, Folder 56)
  - Yangtze River (annotated)
    - Yangtze River n.d. (Box 62, Folder 56)
  - Military Scenes
    - Japanese Army n.d. (Box 62, Folder 57)
  - Military Scenes
    - Russo-Japanese War n.d. (Box 62, Folder 57)
  - Group Portraits (mounted)
    - People, Unidentified Groups n.d. (Box 62, Folder 58)
  - Groups Portraits
    - Portraits n.d. (Box 62, Folder 58)
  - Scenes of China
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Scenes of China
    - China, Peking n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Scenes of China
    - Jade Green Cloud Temple n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Scenes of China
    - Landscapes n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Scenes of China
    - Palaces n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Scenes of China
    - Summer Palace n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Scenes of China
    - Temples n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Temple of Heaven (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Temple of Heaven (annotated)
    - China, Peking n.d. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Temple of Heaven (annotated)
    - Sculpture n.d. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Temple of Heaven (annotated)
    - Temple of Heaven, Peking n.d. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Temple of Heaven (annotated)
    - Temples n.d. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Views of Peking (annotated)
    - Camel Caravans 1910c. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Views of Peking (annotated)
    - China, Peking 1910c. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Views of Peking (annotated)
    - City Scenes 1910c. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Views of Peking (annotated)
    - Forbidden City 1910c. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Views of Peking (annotated)
    - Gates 1910c. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Views of Peking (annotated)
    - Street Scenes 1910c. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Views of Peking (annotated)
    - Tartar Wall 1910c. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Views of Peking (annotated)
    - Transportation, Camel Caravans 1910c. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Views of Peking (annotated)
    - Walls 1910c. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Legation, Peking (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1909 c. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Legation, Peking (annotated)
    - China, Peking 1909c (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Legation, Peking (annotated)
    - Gardens 1909c. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Legation, Peking (annotated)
    - Gates 1909c. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Legation, Peking (annotated)
    - U.S. Legation, Peking 1909c. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Peking Home, Construction
    - Construction 1911 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Peking Home, Construction
    - Residence, Peking 1911 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Peking Home, Construction
    - Architecture, Exterior 1911 c. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Peking Home, Construction
    - China, Peking 1911c. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Peking Home, Construction
    - Construction 1911 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Peking Home, Construction
    - Residence, Peking 1911 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Peking Home, Construction
    - Architecture, Interior 1911 c. (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Peking Home, Construction
    - China, Peking 1911c. (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Peking Home
    - Architecture, Interior 1911 c. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Peking Home
    - China, Peking 1911c. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Peking Home
    - Fireplaces 1911c. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Peking Home (annotated)
    - Residence, Peking 1911 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Siberia
    - Railroads 1907 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Siberia
    - Children 1907c. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Siberia
    - Egan, Eleanor 1907c. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Siberia
    - Egan, Martin 1907c. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Siberia
    - Landscapes 1907c. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Siberia
    - Marvin, George D. 1907c. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Siberia
    - Russia, Siberia 1907c. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Siberia
    - Russia, Vladivostok 1907c. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Siberia
    - Straight, Willard D. 1907c. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Siberia
    - Street Scenes 1907c. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Siberia
    - Transportation, Horsecarts 1907c. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Siberia
    - Transportation, Horse-Drawn Sleighs 1907c. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Siberia
    - Transportation, Railroads 1907c. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Siberia
    - Winter Scenes 1907c. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Yellow Temple, Lama Temple (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Yellow Temple, Lama Temple (annotated)
    - China, Peking n.d. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Yellow Temple, Lama Temple (annotated)
    - Lama Temple n.d. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Yellow Temple, Lama Temple (annotated)
    - Priests n.d. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Yellow Temple, Lama Temple (annotated)
    - Sculpture n.d. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Yellow Temple, Lama Temple (annotated)
    - Temples n.d. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Yellow Temple, Lama Temple (annotated)
    - Yellow Temple n.d. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Winter Palace (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Winter Palace (annotated)
    - Boats n.d. (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Winter Palace (annotated)
    - Bridges n.d. (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Winter Palace (annotated)
    - China, Peking n.d. (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Winter Palace (annotated)
    - River Scenes n.d. (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Winter Palace (annotated)
    - Winter Palace n.d. (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Summer Palace (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Summer Palace (annotated)
    - China, Peking n.d. (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Summer Palace (annotated)
    - Marble Boat n.d. (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Summer Palace (annotated)
    - River Scenes n.d. (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Summer Palace (annotated)
    - Sculpture n.d. (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Summer Palace (annotated)
    - Summer Palace n.d. (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Temple of Heaven (annotated)
    - Altars n.d. (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Temple of Heaven (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Temple of Heaven (annotated)
    - China, Peking n.d. (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Temple of Heaven (annotated)
    - Sculpture n.d. (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Temple of Heaven (annotated)
    - Spirit Walk n.d. (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Temple of Heaven (annotated)
    - Temple of Heaven, Peking n.d. (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Temple of Heaven (annotated)
    - Temples n.d. (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Ming Tombs (annotated)
    - Arches n.d. (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Ming Tombs (annotated)
    - Landscapes n.d. (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Ming Tombs (annotated)
    - Ming Tombs n.d. (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Ming Tombs (annotated)
    - Sculpture n.d. (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Ming Tombs (annotated)
    - Tombs n.d. (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Great Wall
    - Great Wall n.d. (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Great Wall
    - Landscapes n.d. (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Great Wall
    - Nankou Pass n.d. (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Great Wall
    - Bland, John O.P. n.d. (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Great Wall
    - Great Wall n.d. (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Great Wall
    - Landscapes n.d. (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Great Wall
    - Railroads n.d. (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Great Wall
    - Transportation, Donkeys n.d. (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Great Wall
    - Transportation, Railroads n.d. (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Great Wall
    - Vendors n.d. (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Entrances, Arches, Palaces, Temples (annotated)
    - Arches n.d. (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Entrances, Arches, Palaces, Temples (annotated)
    - Architectural Detail n.d. (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Entrances, Arches, Palaces, Temples (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Entrances, Arches, Palaces, Temples (annotated)
    - China, Peking n.d. (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Entrances, Arches, Palaces, Temples (annotated)
    - Gates n.d. (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Entrances, Arches, Palaces, Temples (annotated)
    - Palaces n.d. (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Entrances, Arches, Palaces, Temples (annotated)
    - Temples n.d. (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Street Scenes
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Street Scenes (annotated)
    - China, Peking n.d. (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Street Scenes (annotated)
    - City Scenes n.d. (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Street Scenes (annotated)
    - Forbidden City n.d. (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Street Scenes (annotated)
    - Gates n.d. (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Street Scenes (annotated)
    - Street Scenes n.d. (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Chinese Views
    - Bridges n.d. (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Chinese Views
    - Gardens n.d. (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Chinese Views
    - Landscapes n.d. (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Chinese Scenes (annotated)
    - Children n.d. (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Chinese Scenes (annotated)
    - Chinese Army n.d. (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Chinese Scenes (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Chinese n.d. (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Chinese Scenes (annotated)
    - Women n.d. (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - People (annotated)
    - Children n.d. (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - People (annotated)
    - China n.d. (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - People (annotated)
    - Dress n.d. (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - People (annotated)
    - Korea n.d. (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - People (annotated)
    - Korean Army, Officers n.d. (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - People (annotated)
    - Occupations n.d. (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - People (annotated)
    - Women n.d. (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Chinese Village Scenes
    - Rural Scenes n.d. (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Chinese Village Scenes
    - Transportation, Donkey Carts n.d. (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Chinese Village Scenes
    - Transportation, Horsecarts n.d. (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Chinese Village Scenes
    - Village Scenes n.d. (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Chinese Architecture
    - Pagodas n.d. (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Architecture
    - Pi Yun San n.d. (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Architecture
    - Roofs n.d. (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Architecture (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Architecture (annotated)
    - Bell Tower n.d. (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Architecture (annotated)
    - China, Peking n.d. (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Architecture (annotated)
    - City Scenes n.d. (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Architecture (annotated)
    - Sculpture n.d. (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Architecture
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Transportation (annotated)
    - Camel Caravans n.d. (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Transportation (annotated)
    - Great Wall n.d. (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Transportation (annotated)
    - Transportation, Camel Caravans n.d. (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Transportation (annotated)
    - Transportation, Horsecarts n.d. (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Transportation (annotated)
    - Transportation, Jinrikshas n.d. (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Transportation (annotated)
    - Transportation, Railroads n.d. (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Transportation (annotated)
    - Transportation, Sedan Chairs n.d. (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Transportaton (annotated)
    - Railroads n.d. (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Transportaton (annotated)
    - Railroads, Locomotives n.d. (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Transportaton (annotated)
    - Railroads, Narrow-Gauge n.d. (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Transportaton (annotated)
    - Railroads, Stations n.d. (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Rivers, Docks, and Boats (annotated)
    - Boats n.d. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Rivers, Docks, and Boats (annotated)
    - Bridges n.d. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Rivers, Docks, and Boats (annotated)
    - China, Hankow n.d. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Rivers, Docks, and Boats (annotated)
    - China, Hanyang n.d. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Rivers, Docks, and Boats (annotated)
    - China, Kowloon n.d. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Rivers, Docks, and Boats (annotated)
    - Docks n.d. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Rivers, Docks, and Boats (annotated)
    - Fishing Industry n.d. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Rivers, Docks, and Boats (annotated)
    - Hong Kong n.d. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Rivers, Docks, and Boats (annotated)
    - River Scenes n.d. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Rivers, Docks, and Boats (annotated)
    - Seascapes n.d. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Rivers, Docks, and Boats (annotated)
    - Transporation, Sailboats n.d. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Rivers, Docks, and Boats (annotated)
    - Transportation, Houseboats n.d. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Rivers, Docks, and Boats (annotated)
    - Transportation, Junks n.d. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Rivers, Docks, and Boats (annotated)
    - Transportation, Steamships n.d. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Rivers, Docks, and Boats (annotated)
    - Yangtze River n.d. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Chinese River Scenes
    - Boats n.d. (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Chinese River Scenes
    - River Scenes n.d. (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Chinese River Scenes
    - Transporation, Sailboats n.d. (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Chinese River Scenes
    - Transportation, Rowboats n.d. (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Funeral Procession of Empress Dowager
    - Street Scenes 1909 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Funeral Procession of Empress Dowager
    - Tz'U His 1909 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Funeral Procession of the Empress Dowager
    - Ceremonies 1909 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Funeral Procession of the Empress Dowager
    - China, Peking 1909 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Funeral Procession of the Empress Dowager
    - Empress Dowager, Tz'u His 1909 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Funeral Procession of the Empress Dowager
    - Funeral of Empress Dowager 1909 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Funeral Procession of Empress Dowager
    - Street Scenes 1909 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Funeral Procession of Empress Dowager
    - Tz'U His 1909 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Funeral Procession of the Empress Dowager